[16 Years Ago]
Help me!
Help!
I'm here! Please help me!
Gosh, you were here
Hyesung
Are you okay?
Didn't you
get hurt anywhere?
The boy was rescued
from the warehouse
It was my friend
who rescued me
He stayed with me
until I was saved
No, that's not true…
What?
You must've been
freaked out
Yeah, right
That was when
I got claustrophobia
Oh right, I should
write it down too
Okay
Just forget all of this
Speed test!
How did we first meet?
At a home party
through a friend
What did you like
the most about me?
Your look?
So I'm good-looking
to you, right?
Just move along
Where did we
have our first kiss?
Who'd ask such a thing?
Why are you
bailing this one?
Let's say
we did it at home
What?